# JONATHON S. SHULER

(801) 641-5491 jonathon.shuler@gmail.com

# **SKILLS SUMMARY**

Transitioning into a software/web development career where I can use my logical, analytical learning abilities to build and maintain quality applications that maximize user engagement. My personal interests in technology, software, and lifetime learning will be a valuable asset to your development team.

**Tools/Technologies**: Personal/Academic experience in Java, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, MySQL, PHP, Apache/WAMP, Eclipse, Oracle SQL, JSON, Bootstrap, ¡Query.

Systems: Windows, Linux, MacOS, Windows Server, Android.

**GitHub**: github.com/jonathonShuler

Master of Science, Information Systems

Personal Website: jonathonshuler.github.io

#### EDUCATIONAL EXPERIENCE

# The University of Utah

Salt Lake City, UT

April 2017 Graduation

• 4.0 GPA

- Awarded a Graduate Fellowship based on leadership potential, exceptional merit, and GRE scores (170 Verbal, 163 Quantitative).
- Master's project: created a new application to track student progress within the Information Systems Master's program. Designed to help managers track student success and program statistics.
- Coursework in IT Security, Data Mining, Web Application Development, Data Structures, Systems Analysis & Design, Database, and Networking.
- Applied beginner level experience with Java, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, SQL, and PHP.

Bachelor of Science, Finance

December 2010 Graduation

- Awarded the Honors-At-Entrance scholarship for outstanding academic achievement.
- Extensive coursework in Finance, Accounting, Mathematics, and Science.

## OTHER PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

## **Fidelity Investments**

Salt Lake City, UT

High Net Worth Financial Representative

November 2012 – January 2016

- Manage client relationships, interactions, and accounts.
- Analyze the financial implications of mutual fund, stock, and options transactions often involving large and complex investment portfolios.
- Employed CRM, database, performance analysis, and streaming data applications.

Financial Representative/Premium Relationship Associate(Sales)

June 2011 – November 2012

- Exceptional performance on FINRA licensing exams (98% Series 7 exam score).
- Mastered financial service skills assisting clients with stock trading and mutual fund purchases.
- Strong communication with clients regarding complex investments and concepts.

## Aspire Design, Inc.

Sandy, UT

Operations Assistant/Analyst

Aug. 2010 – June 2011 & Feb. 2007 – Jun. 2008

- Self-taught portions of VBA programming to automate inventory records.
- Analyzed and maintained warehouse inventory data using Excel and CITRIX database.